unaided and So so he did this
kind of like amazing feat.
He walked either to the article
the Antarctic pole unaided and when
he got back he was
completely bankrupt and So
and also a bit of a nutter from what
I'm just going to tell you this so so what
he did was he responded to being
completely bankrupt by
Writing a letter to John
Mills the actor Saying it's your
fault that I became an explorer
because I saw your films got the
Antarctic And that was
the thing that inspired
me to be an explorer
and and now, look at me,
I'm in trouble and like my wife's
leaving me and like I'm I'm kind
of like completely in
debt and everything and
John John Mills replied by saying
come round for tea We start,
you know, but
not as write your letters.
It's like it's a brave thing to do so
kind of a you went around to John Mills'
house for tea and and John Mills said,
okay, like you know, tell me what's going
on And it's like, you know, I've got
all these debts and come what you know I
mean all this kind of financial trouble
and living and John Mills said We're
gonna have to talk you out He said
no, I can't I've talked to the banks.
I can't you know, they're
not listening He said no,
no, no come in the bathroom
So he said like they spent the
rest of the afternoon
in the bathroom Putting
together a talk putting together
an inspirational talk Because like,
you know
John Mills is an actor
And so he said like,
you know, this is what you're gonna
do now you're gonna go around and
talk to people about
walking to the Antarctic,
wherever it was and You that is gonna
be inspiring and you're
going to make money
and he said, you know, this is what
I do now I'm an after dinner speaker.
I'm an inspirational speaker
and it's all down to John Mills